KATE PRASOLEK

kate.prasolek@gmail.com | 07479929600 | London E1 4RS

kateprasolek.github.io/portfolio | behance.net/kateprasolek | linkedin.com/in/kateprasolek

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable graphic designer with a friendly, can-do attitude, experienced in both print and digital design. Self-learner of HTML, CSS and website design with good fundamentals of UI/UX best practices. Crafter with a natural eye for detail, layout and typography, currently exploring motion design field.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

| Adobe Photoshop | (4 years) | HTML, CSS | (2 years) | Dotdigital Emails | (2 years) |
|---------------------|-----------|---------------------|-----------|-------------------|-----------|
| Adobe inDesign | (4 years) | Adobe XD | (1 year) | Litmus | (2 years) |
| Adobe Illustrator | (4 years) | Bootstrap | (2 years) | Git / Github | (2 years) |
| Adobe After Effects | (new) | Google Web Designer | (new) | Wordpress CMS | (5 years) |

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Graphic Designer at Black Women in Leadership Network, London (Nov 2020 - present)

- Create digital graphical assets for the website, newsletter and social media channels (Twitter, Linkedin).
- Develop coherent brand guidelines and create easy to use templates.
- Create video intros and outros.

Graphic Digital Designer at arteKatie Handmade Cards, London (Jan 2020 - present)

- Establish the brand identity, create a new logo, product photography and photo retouching.
- Produce social media graphics (Instagram, Facebook), banners and promotional marketing collateral.
- Update online marketplace websites, create a blog and social media posts, build landing pages.
- Maintain assets libraries and files organised, keep track of sales and expenses.

 I achieved 50% sales and engagement increase by consistent visuals and social media campaigns.

Freelance Graphic Designer at Naturewatch Foundation, London (May 2020 - Oct 2020)

- Communicate with Campaign Coordinator to create engaging website banners and social media assets.
- Design a printed version of the Compassionate Shopping Guide booklet to the brief and budget. I lowered the printing cost by layout changes and offering a different printing company.
- Website redesign.

Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

- Create from brief to completion a wide range of marketing communications such as website banners, emails, gifs, brochures, leaflets, magazine's ads, large format prints and more.
- Work collaboratively with other teams and use feedback to produce final marketing creatives.
- Ensure compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all formats and channels.
- Manage multiple digital and print projects simultaneously adhering to meet deadlines.
- Supervise magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers and printers.
- Maintain templates and files, where I implemented a system that sped up the team's work-flow.

Freelance Graphic Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

Create engaging logos, t-shirts, banners, brochures, leaflets and marketing materials for various clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Receptionist and Research Bank Worker at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Nov 2017)

Reception duties and data administration. I put into practice a structured data entry process, that was easier for volunteers to understand and lower the number of mistakes.

Master Team Member at Paul UK (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays and stock, handling orders, sales plans distribution, reporting and customer service. I achieved a 5% increase in sales by visually managing displays throughout the day.

Saleswoman at Polkomtel SA (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera (May 2009 - Sep 2010)

Organising shifts, stock and deliveries, reporting.

INTERPERSONAL SOFT SKILLS

| Attention to detail | Reliability | Time management | Can-do attitude |
|---------------------|-----------------|---------------------|-----------------------|
| Creativity | Professionalism | Organisation skills | Ability to teamwork |
| Fast-learning | Enthusiasm | Prioritising | Communications skills |

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

| 2020 | Adobe CC After Effects and XD Experience Design, website /UI design. |
|---------|---|
| 2018-19 | Dotmailer/ Dotdigital, Adobe CC Illustrator. |
| 2017 | Adobe Dreamweaver, HTML emails, HTML5/ CSS3, Javascript, jQuery. |
| 2016 | Graphic Design, Layouts and Composition, Branding and Typography, Adobe Creative Suite Photoshop and inDesign. |
| 2008 | Psychology, master degree, Silesian University. |